// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],


}



export var cards = {
  "alpha": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">α</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "alpha"
  },
  "beta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">β</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "bêta"
  },
  "gamma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">γ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "gamma"
  },
  "delta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">δ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "delta"
  },
  "epsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ε</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "epsilon"
  },
  "zeta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ζ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "zêta"
  },
  "eta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">η</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "êta"
  },
  "theta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">θ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "thêta"
  },
  "iota": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ι</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "iota"
  },
  "kappa": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">κ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "kappa"
  },
  "lambda": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">λ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "lambda"
  },
  "lambda": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">λ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "lambda"
  },
  "mu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">μ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "mu"
  },
  "nu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ν</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "nu"
  },
  "xi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ξ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "xi"
  },
  "omicron": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ο</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "omicron"
  },
  "pi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">π</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "pi"
  },
  "rho": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ρ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "rhô"
  },
  "sigma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">σ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "sigma"
  },
  "tau": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">τ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "tau"
  },
  "upsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">υ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "upsilon"
  },
  "phi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">φ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "phi"
  },
  "chi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">χ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "chi"
  },
  "psi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ψ</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "psi"
  },
  "omega": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<div class="greek">ω</div>',
    prompt: "Nom de cette lettre ?",
    answer: "oméga"
  }
};